[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Heidi, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Happy wife, happy life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "VB", "POS", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Why don't we leave your husband out of this for the time being?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Come on, let's do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "You're quite bossy, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Do you always get your own way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "But you see you did it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "I mean, you boss him around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "He's big, but he's very gentle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have met Seal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Because it felt like the pair of you had been sort of searching for each other and then you collided, and you have this extraordinary life with hundreds of children and fabulously successful careers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Four.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Was it really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "What were you both doing there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "I was just visiting a friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "You knew him, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I hadn't met him before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "And did he know you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "So what happened next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I told him to sit down, have a pizza with us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Literally, like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "And he hasn't got a clue you're Heidi Klum the supermodel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi Klum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "He doesn't know, seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "So what happens then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Then we met each other again, but always with friends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "It was pretty good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "It went like this and normally we'd go and we just went like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "And who gripped who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "We both gripped each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "And what were you thinking in that second?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I got really hot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Did you think this is the guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "I was like, oh, wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Had you kissed lots of frogs to get to this point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Otherwise, things just don't get done, do they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "So you squeeze hands, and then you get married.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "He had an igloo built on a mountain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Wait, what was the song?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "He just made something up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "How could any woman resist this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 214, "question": "And what were his exact words of proposal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "\"Do you want to marry me?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What did you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I said yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Henry"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "And then what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "And then nine months later Henry was born.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "How do you be a mother to four children with everything else you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "You know, I don't know how that happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP"], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Are there any more planned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "RBR", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "No, that's it", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Do you like working with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "How do you keep this skinny figure that you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you started it would be nine seasons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "No way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "-- right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Did I pronounce that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Was that always the dream for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "You conquered the world of modeling, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "A little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "-- exciting moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Every one and it still is, because everyone is a little step again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Not thin enough and too short?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "For this industry, yes, because the designers, such as him, they require the girls to be a certain weight, height and size.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 416, "question": "And, also, it's dangerous sort of nonsense that he's starting, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I mean, I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 424, "question": "If I don't, I go back to Germany and I do something else, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "I mean, there is a danger --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Any -- any scalpel at any stage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Would you ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I mean, I don't want to say never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Who are you doing it for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Is your great gift, if you like, the fact that you're secure in yourself, you're self-confident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Yes, I have --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "You like making money, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "That, too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Where did you get that from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I don't know if I'm that smart at it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "ORGAN: Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "That's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'94"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "-- keen to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I've been here since '94.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "How do you think he's doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "That is a tough question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "-- how do the Germans all feel when you when you became an American?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I still am a German, as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Oh, you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Did you ever stop being a German?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I have a dual citizenship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What do you think of America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I really like it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Modern -- in the -- in the modern era, in the last sort of 30, 40 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "In Germany, definitely, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "What's next for the Heidi Klum Incorporated machine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "More designing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi Klum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "From the things -- yes, that I cook up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "-- to, any of them, to get into fashion, would you worry about it, given the experiences you've had?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "I would not push them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "-- a rock star like their dad?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Well I -- I look forward to these kids growing up, actually, because they must -- they're going to look great and be very talented, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Oh, they're a lot of fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "What's your proudest achievement, you personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Oh, my family for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "And then what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "And you come home to a guy who just gets on bended knee in igloos and sings you crazy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'80s"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Who would've thought that to be 80s in Britain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "We survived the '80s.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "But when you come to America now, how's it changed in all senses from when you first came out here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "How was L.A. when we first came here, first?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Boring.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andy Taylor", "Duran Duran"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "So how did you get kicked out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "Andy Taylor, who was a guitarist with Duran Duran, was standing on top of the hotel where there's a pool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Modern bands just don't do this kind of thing, do they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "They haven't lived.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "Really you're not a proper rock star, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "E BON: Bloody jordies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "How are you finding the changing style of music?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "Vinyl is here, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "How do you guys listen to music yourselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "Well, ideally, I listen to music like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Do all of you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Why do you prefer it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "It's better quality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Vinyl is better, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "It's a better sound.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "Is it, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "It's a ritual, putting it on, getting it oust sleeve, making sure that there's no fluff on it, and putting it on and putting the needle on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "Are you guys on iTunes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "We are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "Or is all the money now just, from as I hear it, from touring and merchandise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "Well, obviously, there's been enormous problems with illegal downloads, which has affected the entire industry in a massive way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "How did you -- when you came on stage, how did you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "Terrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fiona", "Simon"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 835, "question": "Which way around was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 836, "answer": "Well, actually, there was a middle person, Fiona, that Simon was living with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "Or you never really crossed that barrier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "It was something a little opportunistic about that, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 867, "question": "Did he really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBD", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 872, "question": "Or how did he revive the Duran magic, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 873, "answer": "Well, I think really what Mark did was focus our attention on what we're good at.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 877, "question": "Was it reminding you, as a fan, was it reminding you of what you're all really good at, or was it making you more adaptable to the modern market?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 878, "answer": "He said you don't have to try, you just have to do what you do, and that's what people want from you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 886, "question": "When you see what happened to Amy, what do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 887, "answer": "Well, I think we were fortunate that we were a band, first of all, and that we always had each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 901, "question": "She got so thin, didn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 902, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "Did you not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 920, "question": "Are these old fans of yours who've come with you or do you have a new breed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 921, "answer": "A mix.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 970, "question": "We're never speaking again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 971, "answer": "I think being a band goes beyond friendship, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "VBG", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 983, "question": "Do you have a genuine ambition, or is it to keep going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 984, "answer": "I think the keeping going and to create a body of work is one of the big ambitions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 997, "question": "Is it more of a primitive, because I would imagine you would be the first in that kind of stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 998, "answer": "I like the idea of it, but I think, one, it is very time consuming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Coachella"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1004, "question": "Would you be in agreement you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1005, "answer": "Well, you know, Coachella was great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1011, "question": "Was it the best ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1012, "answer": "I think to that point --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 1013, "question": "ORGAN: Even at the height of the mania?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1014, "answer": "You can't just pick one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Cuccurullo"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1022, "question": "In Duran Duran history?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1023, "answer": "Well, the Warren Cuccurullo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1027, "question": "When was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1028, "answer": "Pink Flamingos.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1029, "question": "Pink Flamingo?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1030, "answer": "The groom wore more makeup than the bride.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1037, "question": "I mean, you do for this show, but do you normally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1038, "answer": "It's a tattoo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1039, "question": "When you're going out, do you still get the old gear on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1040, "answer": "If I feel like it, you never know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1043, "question": "Simon, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1044, "answer": "If I feel I need it, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 1051, "question": "Who is the best other singer you have ever seen live?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1052, "answer": "Well, I love --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1061, "question": "It's all about now, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1062, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]